PAWEŁ KRÓL

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS (SCSS)
- JavaScript
- GIT
- React
- Webpack
- Figma
- Gatsby
- Firebase

Basics:

- GraphQL
- React Native

LANGUAGUES

Polish - native English - B2 (FCE and LCCI 3 certificates)

PERSONAL INFORMATION

+48 530671067 kontakt@pavkrol.pl www.pavkrol.pl

Github:

https://github.com/pavkrol Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/pavkrol

I hereby consent to my personal data being processed for the purpose of considering my application in the recruitment process.

JOB OBJECTIVE

For the last two years, I have worked at AN-GAZ company, where I was responsible for sales development and product delivery organization. I spent the last year on intensive learning of front-end technologies. In the near future I want to develop my skills further in React, and then towards a full-stack developer.

PROJECTS

Eventify CODE PREVIEW

React application allowing to search and save in database (Firebase) favourite concerts and music artists.

Yahtzee CODE PREVIEW

Dice game - Yahtzee. Application was created in React. Highscores are saving in Firebase.

Coffee Republic CODE PREVIEW

Fictional company website, created with Gatsby and GraphQL.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SALES SPECIALIST

AN-GAZ Dystrybucja Gazu | July 2017 - present

COMMODITY BUYER

Bank BPH / Alior Bank | August 2016 - March 2017

Running savings projects. Management of supplier selection process. Negotiations with suppliers.

CUSTOMER LOYALTY SPECIALIST

Bank BPH | May 2015 - July 2016

Complaint analysis for detecting irregularities. Carrying out corrective actions in processes. Coordinating customer satisfaction surveys.

BUSINESS CUSTOMERS SERVICE SPECIALIST

Bank BPH | August 2010 - May 2015

Handling credit applications and resolving complaints. Participation in projects implementing new products and functionalities.

CALL CENTER SPECIALIST

Bank BPH | August 2008 - July 2010

EDUCATION

ECONOMICS
BACHELOR DEGREE

WSB University in Gdynia | 2012 - 2015